Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pennsylvania State Senate, 2000-2015; 2004-2013; II.
  - Alphabetical Subject Files, 2000-2014; 2003-2008; 1.
    - Mon-Fayette, 2007-2009 (Box 63, Folder 41)
    - MSI Corporation Bridge Project, 2005 (Box 63, Folder 42)
    - Music Therapy, 2005-2013 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - MWBE, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Nano Material Commercialization, undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 2004-2006 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - National Conference of State Leg., undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Natrona Comes Together, 2008-2012 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Natrona Heights District Office, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Natrona Heritage Oak Steel and Miner Sculpture Project, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Neighbors in the Strip, ca 2006 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - New Americans, 2014 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - New Bethel Baptist Ministry, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - News Releases, 2003-2008 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - News Releases, 2009-2010 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - News Releases, 2011-2014 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - North Hills Community Outreach, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Northshore Port Authority Connector Tunnel, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 16-17)
    - Northside Partnership Agreement with Allegheny General Hospital, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - NRA Convention, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - NRG Energy, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Nuclear Plant Monitoring, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Nursing Home Assessment, 2003-2005 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - O'Hara Township, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Offenders- Nonviolent, 2002-2005 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Ohio River Basin, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Ohio River Watershed, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Older and Wiser, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - PA Capital Preservation Committee, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - PA Community Values Survey, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - PA Health Care, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - PA Institute for Conservation Education, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - PA Insurance Department Public Hearing, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - PA School Boards Association, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - PA Tech Formation, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - PA Unified Truck Safety Strategy, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - PA Works, 2011 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - PACE/PACENET, 2005-2006 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Parental Stress Center, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - PCN, undated (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Peabody Technology Grant, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Pediatric Care, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - PennDOT in the District, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Persad Center, Inc., undated (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - PGH Action Against Rape, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 45)
    - Phone Directory/Contact Info, 2010 (Box 64, Folder 46)
    - Pitt Men's Study, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 47)
    - Pittsburgh Ballet Theater, 2008-2009 (Box 64, Folder 48)
    - Pittsburgh Brewery Site, 2012 (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - Pittsburgh Brewing Company, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - Pittsburgh Casino, ca 2003 (Box 64, Folder 51)
    - Pittsburgh Center for the Arts, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 52)
    - Pittsburgh Climate Initiative, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 53)
    - Pittsburgh Community Services, Inc., ca 2007 (Box 64, Folder 54)
    - Pittsburgh Council on the Arts, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 55)
    - Pittsburgh Digital Greenhouse, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Downtown Plan, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Film Office, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Film Office, 2010 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh Glass Center, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh Green Innovators Flagship Campus, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Green Innovators, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh Green Innovators, 2010 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Green Innovators, 2012 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation (PHLF), 2011 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh International Airport, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Mills, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Pittsburgh Neighborhoods, 2005-2006 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Pittsburgh Schools, 2006-2007 (Box 65, Folder 14-15)
    - Pittsburgh Water and Sewer Authority Wet Weather Feasibility Study, 2012-2013 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh Water and Sewer Authority, September 2010 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh-Mantanzas Sister City Project, 2001-2005 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Plan for a New PA, undated (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - PNC Bank Development, 2005 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Point Park University, 2007-2008 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Point State Park, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Police, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Policy Research: Workforce Investment, 2009 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Port Authority, 2007-2009 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - PPND, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Prayer (Senate), 2007 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Predatory Lending Studies, 2005-2006 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Predatory Lending Studies, 2005-2006 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Preservation Pittsburgh, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Preservation, PA, 2010 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Problem Gambling, 2008-2009 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Project Reports (Shad), 2012 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - PROMISe, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Regatta, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Regional Industrial Development Corp, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Renew PA, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Restaurants and Venues, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - River Ave Hotel, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Roaring Run Watershed, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Route 28 Town Meeting, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Schenley Farms, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Seeding Prosperity and Revitalizing Corridors (SPARC), 2011 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Coalition Community Benefits, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Setoff Debt Collection Program, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Sewage Treatment, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Sharpsburg, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Small Business Advocate, 2003-2004 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Small Business Development Center (Duquesne University), 2006 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Small Business Development Center (University of Pittsburgh), 2006 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Small Business Programs, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Social Worker, undated (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Social Workers, 2011-2012 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Sojourner House, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Speech Pathologists and Audiologists, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Spring Garden Neighborhood Enterprises, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Stanton Negley Drug Co., 2004 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Starr Discount, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - State Correctional Institution (SCI) Pittsburgh, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - State Info/Senate House, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Statewide Uniform Registry of Electors (SURE), 2004 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Steel Valley Authority, 2007-2012 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Steinbrenner Institute (Carnegie Mellon University) (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Stormwater Management, 2013 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Strip District, undated (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program (SNAP), 2012 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Sustainability, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Target Employment Project II, 2010-2011 (Box 66, Folder 37-38)
    - Technology, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Thomas Consulting, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Transit Development Plan (TDP) for District 38, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Transit-Oriented Development (Bridging the Busway), ca. 2010 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Transportation, 2003-2007 (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Transportation, 2012 (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Troy Hill Heart of Troy Hill Plan, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Truancy, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - Truancy, 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - U.S. Constitution, undated (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - Union Info, undated (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - Union Painters & Allied Trades, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 50)
    - University of Pittsburgh Office of Technology Management, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 51)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 52)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 53)
    - UPMC, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 54)
    - Vandergrift, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 55)
    - Victim Advocate (Carol Labery), undated (Box 66, Folder 56)
    - Walmart, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 57)
    - Walsh's Bar, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 58)
    - Washington Crossing, 2010 (Box 66, Folder 59)
    - Water Quality, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 60)
    - Westinghouse Railroad Airbrake Historical Marker Nomination, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 61)
    - WIC, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 62)
    - Wine Association, 2007-2009 (Box 66, Folder 63)
    - Wire Taps, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 64)
    - Workers Compensation Appeals Board, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 65)
    - Workforce Investment Board, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 66)
    - Wright, Lloyd, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 67)
    - Zero Bar, Inc. (Southside), 2005 (Box 66, Folder 68)
    - Zober, Yarone, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 69)
  - Associations and Commissions, 2002-2011; 2004-2008; 2.
    The Associations and Commissions subseries contains materials related to a variety of Pittsburgh and Pennsylvania area organizations that Ferlo was either a member of or was a participant, including the PA Historical and Museum Commission and Public Utilities Commission.
    - Alle-Kiski Coalition, 2002-2006 (Box 66, Folder 70)
    - Ethics Commission, 2011 (Box 66, Folder 71)
    - Fish and Boat Commission, 2005-2006 (Box 66, Folder 72)
    - Kingsley Association, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 73)
    - Lower Bloomfield Unity Council, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 74)
    - PA Aquacultural Advisory Commission, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 75)
    - PA Biodiversity Partnership, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 76)
    - PA Department of Community and Economic Development, undated (Box 66, Folder 77)
    - PA Economic Development Association, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 78)
    - PA Hardwood Development Council, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 79)
    - PA Historical and Museum Commission, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - PA Historical and Museum Commission, 2007 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - PA Historical and Museum Commission, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - PA Historical and Museum Commission, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - PA Historical and Museum Commission, 2010 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - PA Low Income Housing Coalition, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - PA Septage Management Association, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - PA State Association of Boroughs, 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - PA State Association of Township Supervisors, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - PA State Athletic Commission, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Oversight Board, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Pittsburgh Parking Authority, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Port of Pittsburgh Commission, 2005-2006 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Port of Pittsburgh Commission, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Public Utilities Commission (PUC), 2003 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Public Utility Commission (PUC) Call Center, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Public Utility Commission (PUC) Consumer Information, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Southwestern PA Commission, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Subsidized Child Care Advisory Subcommittee, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Technology Collaborative, 2005-2006 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Technology Education Association of PA, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Township Supervisors, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Legislation Issues and Correspondence, 2000-2014; 2004-2010; 3.
    The Legislation Issues and Correspondence subseries contains materials related to Pennsylvania and regional organizations and issues, including Chapter 30 and broadband network agreements, healthcare legislation, gaming licensing, natural gas and Marcellus shale regulation, municipal pension reform, public school and state employee's retirement systems reform and public utilities and electricity issues and agreements.
    - Alphabetical Subject File, 2000-2014
      - AARP, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Abate of PA, 2003-2004 (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Abortion Legislation (S.B. 732), 2011 (Box 67, Folder 25)
      - Abortion, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      - Access Charges, 2009-2010 (Box 67, Folder 27)
      - Accuarial Notes, 2009-2010 (Box 67, Folder 28)
      - ACRE Legislation, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 29)
      - Act 47 (Distressed Communities Designation), 2007-2012 (Box 67, Folder 30)
      - Act 72 (Homestead/Farmstead Act), 2005 (Box 67, Folder 31)
      - Acupuncture Registration Act, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 32)
      - Adult Basic Healthcare, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 33)
      - Affordable Care Act, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 34)
      - Airport Security, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 35)
      - Allegheny County Pension Preservation Bill, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 36)
      - Allegheny County Retirement Board, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 37)
      - Allegheny County Sportsmen's League, 2001-2002 (Box 67, Folder 38)
      - Allegheny General Hospital Nurses Contract, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 39)
      - All-Terrain Vehicles, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 40)
      - Alternative Ratemaking Mechanism/Distribution System Improvement Charge, 2012 (Box 67, Folder 41)
      - Appraisers, 2013 (Box 67, Folder 42)
      - Apprenticeships, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 43)
      - Architects, 2014 (Box 67, Folder 44)
      - Back-End Referendum, 2004 (Box 67, Folder 45)
      - Bank Robbery, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 46)
      - Banking, 2011 (Box 67, Folder 47)
      - Beer Sales, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 48)
      - Bid Limits, 2007-2009 (Box 67, Folder 49)
      - Bill Analysis Template, 2003 (Box 67, Folder 50)
      - Bill Memos, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 51)
      - Binding Arbitration, 2005-2013 (Box 67, Folder 52)
      - Blight Bills, 2001-2012 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
      - Brownfield Remediation, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Campaign Finance Reform, 2010 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Car Dealers, 2013 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Carbon Monoxide, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Castle Doctrine, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Certificate of Need Program, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Charter Schools, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Children's Health Insurance Program (CHIP), 2010-2013 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Citizen's Action for a Safe Environment (CASE), 2003 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Civil Right Initiative, 2000-2005 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Civil Right Initiative, 2000-2005 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Clean Energy Programs, 2003-2009 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Clean Energy Programs, 2003-2009 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Clean Water Action, 2003-2008 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Coach's Bill (Act 234), 2003 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Community Action Association of PA, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Consolidated EIT Communications, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Consumer Credit Code, 2006 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - County Conservation Districts, 2005-2006 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Credit Counseling, 2007-2008 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Crematoriums, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Criminal Justice System, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Darfur Emergency Coalition of Pittsburgh, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - Death Penalty, 2003-2008 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - Deer Management Plan, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - Dental Association of PA, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 28)
      - Disabilities, 2005-2013 (Box 68, Folder 29)
      - Disabilities: Office for People with Disabilities, 2003-2006 (Box 68, Folder 30)
      - Dispute Resolution for Homebuyer/Homebuilders, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - District Attorneys: Full Time, 2004 (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - Divestment, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - DNA Evidence, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Domestic Partnership Benefits, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - Donated and Dedicated Property Act, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 36)
      - Driving with Mobile Phones, 2005-2011 (Box 68, Folder 37)
      - Driving with Mobile Phones, 2005-2011 (Box 68, Folder 38)
      - Driving with Mobile Phones, 2005-2011 (Box 68, Folder 39)
      - Drug and Alcohol Programs, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 40)
      - DUI, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 41)
      - Duquesne School District, 2012 (Box 68, Folder 42)
      - Early Childhood Education, 2003-2013 (Box 68, Folder 43)
      - Economic Development, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Education, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - EITC, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Election Reform, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Electric (Variable Rates), 2014 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Electric Choice, 2012 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Electric Reliability, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Electric Vehicles, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Electronic Advertising, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Emergency Contraception, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Emergency Relief Act, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Eminent Domain, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Eminent Domain, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Eminent Domain, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Employee Free Choice Act, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Endangered Species, 2014 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Energy Efficiency, 2012 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Environmental Education, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Evictions, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 19)
      - Factory Farming, 2003-2004 (Box 69, Folder 20)
      - Fair Dealership Law, 2012 (Box 69, Folder 21)
      - Falun Gong, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 22)
      - Fire and Emergency Services, 2004-2006 (Box 69, Folder 23)
      - Firefighters Occupational Cancer, undated (Box 69, Folder 24)
      - Firefighters, 2009-2012 (Box 69, Folder 25)
      - Fishing License Increase, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 26)
      - Fox Chapel, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 27)
      - Fracking Public Hearing Packet, 2013 (Box 69, Folder 28)
      - Fraternal Order of Police, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 29)
      - Furloughs, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 30)
      - Gas, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 31)
      - Gateway Health Plan, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 32)
      - Gay Marriage, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 33)
      - Genealogy, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 34)
      - General Competency Assessment, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 35)
      - Great Lakes Compact, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 36)
      - Gun Violence, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 37)
      - Harrisburg Takeover, 2011 (Box 69, Folder 38)
      - Harrison Township, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 39)
      - Hate Crimes, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 40)
      - Hayes Project, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 41)
      - Hazardous Site Cleanup Fund, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 42)
      - HB 113, 200, 1589, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 43)
      - Healthy People 2010, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 44)
      - Helmet Law, 2003-2013 (Box 69, Folder 45)
      - Hemophilia, 2010 (Box 69, Folder 46)
      - High Risk Pool, 2007-2010 (Box 69, Folder 47)
      - Highmark/IBC Merger, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 48)
      - Historic Preservation Grant, 2006-2010 (Box 69, Folder 49)
      - Holy Family Institute, 2004-2006 (Box 69, Folder 50)
      - Homeowners Emergency Mortgage Assistance Program (HEMAP), 2008-2012 (Box 69, Folder 51)
      - Housing Trust Fund, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 52)
      - Human Relations Act, 2007-2008 (Box 69, Folder 53)
      - Illegal Immigration, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 54)
      - Immunizations, 2013 (Box 69, Folder 55)
      - Innocence Project, 2005-2007 (Box 69, Folder 56)
      - Innocence Project, 2005-2007 (Box 69, Folder 57)
      - Innovate in PA, 2013 (Box 69, Folder 58)
      - Intergovernmental Cooperation Authority, 2005-2008 (Box 69, Folder 59)
      - Interior Design, 2013 (Box 69, Folder 60)
      - Intermediate Units, 2004-2013 (Box 69, Folder 61)
      - Interpreters, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 62)
      - Interpreters, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 63)
      - Joint Conservation Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 69, Folder 64)
      - Jonas Salk, 2006-2008 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Jury Commissioners, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Jury Commissioners, 2011 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Juvenile Justice System, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Keg Loss, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Keystone Opportunity Zone, 2000-2008 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Killbuck Township Landslide, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Labor History, 2003 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Land Recycling Task Force, 2011 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Leadership, 2010 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Legislation (Miscellaneous), 2005-2008 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2005-2006 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2008 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2010 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2010 (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2011 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2012 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2012 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2012 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2013 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2014 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Legislative Information Files, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Legislative Information Files, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Legislative Information Files, undated (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Legislative Reform, 2005-2008 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Letters of Support / Opposition from Constituents, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - LIHEAP, 2004-2007 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Liquor Code, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Liquor Control Board, 2003-2006 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Living Will Law, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Local 85 Amalgamated Transit Union (ATU)- Port Authority, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Long-Term Care, 2013 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Longwall Mining, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Luna Square, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Luna Square, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Maglev, 2005-2008 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Majestic Star, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Marriage, 2006-2008 (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Medical Cannabis, 2014 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Medical Malpractice (Recent Facts), 2003-2009 (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Medical Malpractice (Recent Facts), 2003-2009 (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Medicare Prescription Drug Act, 2005 (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - Medication, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Mercury Emissions, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Mercy Behavioral Health, 2006 (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Merit Selection of Judges, 2008 (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Metropolitan Bank, 2007 (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Minimum Wage, 2005-2007 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Motor Vehicle Sales Finance Act, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Municipal Aggregation, 2010 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Municipal Claims and Tax Lien Law, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Municipal Ordinances, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 5)